International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Industrial Aircraft, Lodge 743 Records 1984.0013
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series X: Accessory Controls Company, 1959-1978
  - Subseries A: Subject Files, 1959-1978
    - Standard & Poors, Federal Sign and Signal Co., 1969
    - Termination, David Marvin
    - Wage and classification review, 1967-1974
    - Wage notes (part-time), 1961-1967
    - Warning notices, 1970-1974
    - Workers' comments on jobs they performs, undated
  - Subseries B: Negotiations and Agreements, 1959-1978
    - Negotiations: correspondence and notes, 1960-1972; (4 folders)
    - Negotiations: minutes, 1972-1978; (3 folders)
    - Proposals (company), 1968
    - Proposals (union), 1968
    - Proposals and agreement, 1974
    - Agreements, 1959-1971; (7 folders)
- Series XI: Local 2126, 1958-1961
  - Agreement: Flight Enterprises Company D-91, 1960
  - Correspondence, 1960-1961
  - Financial Statements, 1959-1960
  - Monthly financial reports (Grand Lodge), 1958-1960
  - Monthly check-off, 1961
  - Monthly membership and per capita tax report and summary, 1958-1960